Contact

knandi@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/krishnendunandi (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

SQL

Solution Architecture
Software Project Management

Krishnendu Nandi

Co-founder Of QuizBee

Hyderabad

Summary

Experienced Business Expert with a demonstrated history of working in the IT industry. Skilled in PL/SQL, UNIX, Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC), Software Project Management, Integration and Production Support. Strong media and communication professional with a Bachelor of Engineering - BE focused in Electronics and Communications Engineering from National Institute of Technology, Silchar.

Experience

QuizBee

Co-founder

August 2016 - Present (4 years 1 month)

Hyderabad Area, India

Online Earning Opportunities
Online Business Expert
August 2010 - July 2016 (6 years)
India

ObjectWin Technology Professional Consultant December 2009 - August 2010 (9 months)

Hyderabad Area, India

Accenture Services
Project Lead
March 2009 - November 2009 (9 months)
Hyderabad Area, India

Mahindra Satyam Project Lead May 2004 - March 2009 (4 years 11 months)

Education

National Institute of Technology Silchar

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Electronics and Communications Engineering

Netaji Subhash Vidyaniketan, Agartala Science